

CONTACT

Email

emrekara.dev@gmail.com

Phone

+90 551 101 4100

GitHub

github.com/emrekaraa

Website

emrekara.dev

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/emrekaraa

Address

Cekmekoy / Istanbul / Turkey

LANGUAGES

Turkish

Native Language

English

B2 - Intermediate Level

EDUCATION

Web Design and Coding

Ankara Univercity
Associate of Arts - Continues

Faculty Of Theology

Anadolu Univercity
Associate Degree - Graduate

EMRE KARA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I have 3+ years experience in Frontend Development especially React.js and Next.js. I describe myself as a JavaScript developer, not a framework developer. I like to try and learn new technologies. I'm passionate about my work. Because I love what I do. I have a steady source of motivation that drives me to do my best.

EXPERIENCE

06/2023 - Now

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Present

Demirören Holding / Yenibiris



I am working on the Yenibiris.com website renewal project. I am also developing an online interview and online exam project.

11/2022 - 06/2023 8 Months FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Sodexo

sodex*o

I have worked on a back office web application used by Sodexo call center users. I am also developed the Sodexo Mobile App and Sodexo Cep Pos App.

10/2022 - 11/2022

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2 Months

Sigma Group



I developed the backend and frontend of the kocyasa.com website. I also developed a content management system for the project.

08/2021 - 10/2022

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

1 Year 2 Months

Tamer Capital



I have worked on multiple projects at the same time. I made web applications, admin panels, official websites and many reusable components.

06/2020 - 08/2021 1 Year 3 Months **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

Freelance



As a freelancer, I developed many fullstack web applications.

Projects: discoveryballoons.com | urgupballoons.com | turquazballoons.com | balloonscanner.com | carstudio.ai

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Frontend

JavaScript TypeScript React.js React Native Next.js

Backend

Node.js Express.js MongoDb PostgreSql

Devops

Linux Shell Aws Cloud NginX Docker CI-CD Pipeline

Others

Postman Git Jira Figma AdobeXD PhotoShop